<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<directors>
	<director>
		<name>Sadie Honchock</name>
		<age>17</age>
		<location>USA</location>
		<pronouns>she/her</pronouns>
		<position>Founder, Executive Director</position>
		<bio>Sadie Honchock is a rising senior at University View Academy where she is pursuing her high school diploma and her Associate's of Arts in Humanities. She is a self-taught artist, author, and youth activist who aspires to be a staff attorney for the ACLU when she is older.</bio>
		<imgurl>sadie.png</imgurl>
	</director>
    
    <director>
        <name>Samira Akbary</name>
        <age>17</age>
        <location>USA</location>
        <pronouns>she/her</pronouns>
        <position>Co-Director of Development and Management</position>
        <bio>Samira is a rising high school senior. At school, she has been a passionate member of Young Dems and held leadership positions in Key Club. Outside of school, she was the founder of Letters 4 Docs, which wrote over 400 COVID-19 relief letters to medical personnel. She is also the Director of Civil Rights Advocacy at the Greater Good Initiative which elevates youth voices in public policy.</bio>
        <imgurl>samira.jpg</imgurl>
    </director>
	
	<director>
		<name>Grace Harrison</name>
		<age>18</age>
		<location>USA</location>
		<pronouns>she/her</pronouns>
		<bio>Grace is a very creative individual, and is passionate about a variety of social justice causes. In her free time, she loves to read, bake, and color. She loves graphic design and her goal is to utilize her Spanish skills in any way she can!</bio>
		<imgurl>blank.jpg</imgurl>
	</director>
	
	<director>
		<name>Lou Weinstein</name>
		<age>21</age>
		<location>Canada</location>
		<pronouns>they/them</pronouns>
		<position>Co-Director of Research</position>
		<bio>Lou is from Atlanta, GA and based in Montréal, QC. They have a passion for social justice, research, and educational advocacy along with entomology, mycology, and botany. They are in their last year of undergraduate before heading to graduate school to pursue medical/scientific illustration; they are also a tattoo artist. If they're not at school, they are usually on the train reading any social justice, advocacy awareness, and/or socialist rhetoric they can get their hands on, gardening on their tiny balcony, tattooing, or drawing/painting!</bio>
		<imgurl>lou.jpg</imgurl>
	</director>
	
	<director>
		<name>Cameron Fischer</name>
		<age>15</age>
		<location>USA</location>
		<pronouns>she/her</pronouns>
		<position>Co-Director of Outreach and Marketing</position>
		<bio>Cameron is a rising Sophomore in Raleigh, NC. She is spends her time in school helping with the student government and tutoring underprivileged elementary students from a local school. She is an advocate for social justice, educational equity, and the climate crisis. In addition to working small scale in her local area, she is part of Fridays for Future Digital. She hopes to go into law or education when she is older.</bio>
		<imgurl>cameron.jpeg</imgurl>
	</director>
	
	<director>
		<name>Erin Reed</name>
		<age>13</age>
		<location>she/her</location>
		<pronouns>USA</pronouns>
		<position>Co-Director of Outreach and Marketing</position>
		<bio>Erin has a wide variety of interests, including the fantasy role-playing game <i>Dungeons and Dragons</i>, character design, and tarot cards. In her free time, she likes to spend time in nature or create comics. She is very passionate about creating art, activism, and social justice.</bio>
		<imgurl>blank.jpg</imgurl>
	</director>
	
    <director>
        <name>Nina Kisanga</name>
        <age>18</age>
        <location>USA</location>
        <pronouns>she/her</pronouns>
        <position>Director of Activism Art</position>
        <bio>Nina is a digital artist from Ohio, and is heading to Tulane University to study Public Health and Political Science/Pre-Law in the fall. In high school, she was involved in political activism, music, and community outreach efforts, and plans to continue these in college. She is very passionate about criminal justice reform, and hopes to work as a public health or civil rights lawyer in the future.</bio>
        <imgurl>nina.jpg</imgurl>
    </director>
	
	<director>
		<name>Ain Hasdi</name>
		<age>15</age>
		<location>USA</location>
		<pronouns>she/her</pronouns>
		<position>Co-Director of Pleasantry Art</position>
		<bio>Ain is very interested in history and English—she particularly enjoys reading novels. She also really loves cats and sunrises. In her free time, you can find her pursuing one of her passions, such as reading or creating art!</bio>
		<imgurl>blank.jpg</imgurl>
	</director>
    
</directors>