<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<directors>
	<director>
		<name>Sadie Honchock</name>
		<age>17</age>
		<location>USA</location>
		<pronouns>she/her</pronouns>
		<position>Founder, Executive Director</position>
		<bio>Sadie Honchock is a rising senior at University View Academy where she is pursuing her high school diploma and her Associate's of Arts in Humanities. She is a self-taught artist, author, and youth activist who aspires to be a staff attorney for the ACLU when she is older.</bio>
		<imgurl>sadie.png</imgurl>
	</director>
	
    <director>
        <name>Megan Cooper</name>
        <age>18</age>
        <location>USA</location>
        <pronouns>she/her</pronouns>
        <position>Co-Director of Development and Management</position>
        <bio>Megan Cooper is heading to Syracuse University in the fall to pursue a double major in Political Science and News/Online Journalism. She is passionate about the possibilities for our future and hopes to work with other young people to create systems that help all people and are not based on oppression of minority groups.</bio>
        <imgurl>megan.jpg</imgurl>
    </director>
    
    <director>
        <name>Samira Akbary</name>
        <age>17</age>
        <location>USA</location>
        <pronouns>she/her</pronouns>
        <position>Co-Director of Development and Management</position>
        <bio>Samira is a rising high school senior. At school, she has been a passionate member of Young Dems and held leadership positions in Key Club. Outside of school, she was the founder of Letters 4 Docs, which wrote over 400 COVID-19 relief letters to medical personnel. She is also the Director of Civil Rights Advocacy at the Greater Good Initiative which elevates youth voices in public policy.</bio>
        <imgurl>samira.jpg</imgurl>
    </director>
	
	<director>
		<name>Lou Weinstein</name>
		<age>21</age>
		<location>Canada</location>
		<pronouns>they/them</pronouns>
		<position>Co-Director of Research</position>
		<bio>Lou is from Atlanta, GA and based in Montréal, QC. They have a passion for social justice, research, and educational advocacy along with entomology, mycology, and botany. They are in their last year of undergraduate before heading to graduate school to pursue medical/scientific illustration; they are also a tattoo artist. If they're not at school, they are usually on the train reading any social justice, advocacy awareness, and/or socialist rhetoric they can get their hands on, gardening on their tiny balcony, tattooing, or drawing/painting!</bio>
		<imgurl>lou.jpg</imgurl>
	</director>
	
	<director>
		<name>Cameron Fischer</name>
		<age>15</age>
		<location>USA</location>
		<pronouns>she/her</pronouns>
		<position>Co-Director of Outreach and Marketing</position>
		<bio>Cameron is a rising Sophomore in Raleigh, NC. She is spends her time in school helping with the student government and tutoring underprivileged elementary students from a local school. She is an advocate for social justice, educational equity, and the climate crisis. In addition to working small scale in her local area, she is part of Fridays for Future Digital. She hopes to go into law or education when she is older.</bio>
		<imgurl>cameron.jpeg</imgurl>
	</director>
	
    <director>
        <name>Nina Kisanga</name>
        <age>18</age>
        <location>USA</location>
        <pronouns>she/her</pronouns>
        <position>Director of Activism Art</position>
        <bio>Nina is a digital artist from Ohio, and is heading to Tulane University to study Public Health and Political Science/Pre-Law in the fall. In high school, she was involved in political activism, music, and community outreach efforts, and plans to continue these in college. She is very passionate about criminal justice reform, and hopes to work as a public health or civil rights lawyer in the future.</bio>
        <imgurl>nina.jpg</imgurl>
    </director>
	
	<director>
		<name>Angelique Herrin</name>
		<age>15</age>
		<location>USA</location>
		<pronouns>she/her</pronouns>
		<position>Co-Director of Pleasantry Art</position>
		<bio>Angelique is a rising sophomore in the USA. She is very passionate about the arts, and activism. At her school, she participates in several performing arts related activities, such as a theater competition team, and makes art in her own freetime.</bio>
		<imgurl>angelique.jpg</imgurl>
	</director>
    
</directors>